

# **Aleksey Kurlovich**

**QA** Engineer

### Profile

QA Engineer with about 1+ year of experience. Testing crypto wallet application, smart contract, nft-scanner, token-scanner, swap, working with two networks (mainnet and testnet). Testing mobile and web application. Experience in developing test documentation: Test Case, Check-list, Bug Report, Test Report.

Currently studying selenium using C# language. Have a small experience in automatization testing.

# Employment History

# InternShip at Qulix Systems, Minsk

November 2022 — December 2022

Responsibilities:

- Testing FE/BE;
- · Design testing;
- Create Test scenarios, report tickets;
- · Smoke, MAT, AT testing;
- · Requirements testing;
- · Design testing.

# QA Engineer at BELKO TECHNOLOGIES, Minsk

October 2021 — October 2022

Responsibilities:

- Testing software development kit's tied with the blockchains such as Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain, Polygon, Terra in case of swap, staking, nft data aggregation;
- Testing FE/BE;
- Testing mobile application;
- Create Test scenarios, report tickets;
- Smoke, MAT, AT testing;
- Scrum.

## Education

BA, BSUIR, Minsk

September 2019 — Feb 2023

Faculty of Computer Systems and Networks. System Engineer

# GitHub

Link to my GitHub: https://github.com/Aliaksei3/Qulix

#### **Details**

Belarus

+375(29)364-04-68 kurlovich11245@gmail.com

#### Links

Linkedin

## **Skills**

Web API

Swagger

Postman

**ISON** 

DevTools

SQL

Jira

Git

YouTrack

Sentry.io

HTML

CSS

# Languages

English A2+